Guide to the Lindbergh Picture Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Charles Augustus Lindbergh, 1902-1974; Series I
  - In Little Falls, Minnesota, 1927 August 26 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    With Evangeline Lodge Land Lindbergh at the Unites States tour reception.
  - In Dearborn, Michigan, 1927 August 27? (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    Two albums of Charles Augustus Lindbergh's visit to Dearborn during his tour of the United States with the Spirit of St. Louis. Includes images of Lindbergh with Edsel and Henry Ford at the Ford factory, as well as in Ford airplane. The albums were sent to Evangeline Lodge Land Lindbergh by Edsel Ford.
  - In Omaha, Nebraska, 1927 August 30-31 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - In Bolling Field, Washington, DC, Circa 1927-1928 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    With "Jack" Masthay and his Ford Trimotor Monoplane.
  - In Seattle, Washington, 1927 September 13-14 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - In Portland, Oregon, 1927 September 15-16 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - In San Francisco, California, 1927 September 16 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - In San Diego, California, 1927 September 23 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - In Los Angeles, California, with Will Rogers, 1927 September 23 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    See also oversize.
  - In Lordsburg, New Mexico, 1927 September 24 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - In Brookhaven, Mississippi, 1927 October (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - In Memphis, Tennessee, 1927 October 3 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - In Spartanburg, North Carolina, 1927 October 12 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - In Richmond, Virginia, 1927 October 16 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - At Dupont Field, Delaware, 1927 October 21 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, airport dedication, 1927 October 22 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - In Washington, DC, 1927 November 14 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Dinner with President Coolidge and other famous aviators at the White House.
  - In Mexico, 1927 December (Box 7, Folder 16)
    On Latin America tour with the Morrow family.
  - In Santa Barbara, California, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    At Chadbourne-Donze air services.
  - In Detroit, Michigan, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Sitting in race car.
  - On a sailboat, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - With Thomas Edison and Henry Ford, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - In Panama, 1928 January 9 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - In Honduras, 1928 January 10 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - In Panama, 1928 January 12-15 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Flying over canal zone.
  - In Panama, 1928 January 20-26 (Box 8, Folder 8-9)
  - Aboard USS Saratoga, 1928 January 27 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - In Dominican Republic, 1928 February 4-6 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - At Lambert Field in St. Louis, Missouri, 1928 February 15 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Return from Havana, Cuba.
  - Flies the airmail, 1928 February 20 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - In Boston, Massachusetts, 1928 February 26 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - With Gene Tunney and Charles Baskerville, 1928 February (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - With Harry Guggenheim, 1928 June 25 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - At the University of Puerto Rico, 1928 September (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Los Angeles Air Races, 1928 September 5 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - At Ford Ranch, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - At solar factory in San Diego, California, Circa 1929-1930 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - In Englewood, New Jersey, 1929 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - With aviators Mayo, Hatch, Tomlinson, and Maddux, Circa 1929 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - With unidentified group, Circa 1929 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - First airmail flight from Miami to Panama, 1929 February 4-13 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - In Barranquilla, Colombia, 1929 February 9 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - In Tampico, Mexico, 1929 March 10 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - On honeymoon with Anne Morrow Lindbergh, 1929 May 27 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    See also: Oversize
  - With Mary Pickford, Amelia Earhart and others, 1929 July 7 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    At the inaugural flight of the first coast-to-coast air service, Transcontinental Air Transport.
  - Maddux Airlines flight to West Coast, Circa 1929 July 7-9 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - At Mitchell Field, 1929 July 9 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Chaco Canyon, New Mexico, 1929 July (Box 8, Folder 31)
    May also include photographs at Canyon de Chelley, Arizona.
  - Enlargements of aerial explorations, 1929 July (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Sent by Carnegie Institution in Washington, DC
  - Southwest United States, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Rock formations and caves.
  - Transcontinental Air Transport route, 1929 July (Box 9, Folder 3-8)
    Consists of aerial views of the Southwest United States.
  - Cleveland Air Races, 1929 August (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - At the Commission of Inquiry and Conciliation, Bolivia and Paraguay, 1929 August (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Yucatán, Mexico, 1929 September (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Mayan ruins, Mexico, 1929 September (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Pan American Airways group?, 1929 September (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - With Juan Trippe, 1929 September 5 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Pan American Airways trip to West Indies, 1929 September 22-29 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - At Lebec camp? in Lebec, California, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Dwight Whitney Morrow's senatorial campaign, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Cristobal France Field, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - In Puerto Rico, Circa 1930 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - In flying gear, Circa 1930 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Flying sailplane, Circa 1930 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - General, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Bowlus glider tests, 1930 January-March (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Commission of Inquiry and Conciliation, 1930 February 7 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Testing the Sirius, 1930 March (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - In Hollywood, California, with the boy scouts, 1930 April (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - With William Birren and the Sirius, 1930 April (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - With Albert Mcleod and Dudley Sterle, 1930 April 30 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - With Harry Guggenheim and Fred Rentschler, 1930 May 3-10 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    New York aircraft show.
  - President Hoover awarding Lindbergh the Congressional Gold Medal, 1930 August 15 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Posing on steps, 1930 December (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - At Princeton University, New Jersey, Circa 1931 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Chichimas?, Circa 1931 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - In cockpit of biplane with Sanford Willets, Circa 1931 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - In Canada, Circa 1931 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Learning to fly Bird biplane, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Onboard HMS Hermes, Circa 1931 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - At College Point and Flushing Bay, New York, 1931 July 27 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - In Arctic, 1931 July 28 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - In North Haven, Maine, 1931 July 30 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Beginning of Pacific survey flight.
  - In Churchill, Canada, 1931 August 2-3 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - In Aklavik, Northwest Territories, 1931 August 5-8 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Point Barrow, Alaska, 1931 August 9 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Nome, Alaska, 1931 August 12-13 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Arrival in Tokyo, Japan, 1931 August 26 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Canadian legation, Tokyo, 1931 August 29 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - On the Lockheed Sirius, 1931 August (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Japanese dignitaries, 1931 August-September (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Japan, 1931 August-September 11 (Box 11, Folder 9-10)
  - In Nanking, China, 1931 September 20-30 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Pan American Airways Sikorsky Clipper, 1931 November (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - With American Clipper, 1931 December (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - General, Circa 1932 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - At Hopewell, New Jersey, with detectives, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - With Mr. and Mrs. Ebeling and Mrs. Carrel, 1932 February 22 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Trans World Airlines (TWA), 1933 February 21 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    With Northrop airmail plane.
  - With Mrs. Beauregard, 1933 April 22 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - In Glendale, California, 1933 May 1 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Onboard The Jelling, 1933 July-August (Box 11, Folder 20)
    The Jelling was an aircraft carrier owned by Pan American Airways, and was used to carry fuel. Lindbergh used it several times on his North Atlantic survey flight.
  - At College Point in Long Island, New York, 1933 July 9 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    Beginning of North Atlantic survey flight.
  - In North Haven, Maine, 1933 July 11 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - In Nova Scotia, Canada, 1933 July 12 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - In Hebron, Labrador, 1933 July 13 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Newfoundland, general, 1933 July 13-20 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - In St. Johns, Newfoundland and Labrador, 1933 July 14-20 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - In Cartwright, Newfoundland and Labrador, 1933 July 14-20 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - In Godthaab, Greenland, 1933 July 21 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - North Atlantic survey flight, place unspecified, Circa 1933 July 20-August 6 (Box 12, Folder 7-12)
  - In Holsteinsborg, Greenland, 1933 July 26-August 4 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Islands in Greenland, 1933 August 4-6 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    The Islands in Greenland that Lindbergh visited were Ella Island, Clavering Island, Eskimones, and Scoresby Sund.
  - In Julianehaab, Greenland, 1933 August 11-12 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - In Angmagsalik, Greenland, 1933 August 13-15 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Iceland, 1933 August 15-23? (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Shetland Islands, Scotland, 1933 August 24-25 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Faroe Islands, Denmark, 1933 August 25 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - In Copenhagen, Denmark, 1933 August 26-September 4 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - In Stockholm, Sweden, 1933 September 4-17 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - In Skane, Sweden, 1933 September 17 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - In Moscow, Russia, 1933 September 22 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Visit to Russia (album), 1933 September 22-29 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - In England, 1933 October 4-23 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - In Paris, France, 1933 October 26-November 4 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - In Holland, 1933 November 4-8 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - In Geneva, Switzerland, 1933 November 8-11 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - In Villa Cisneros, Río de Oro (Africa), 1933 November 12 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - In Cape Verde, 1933 November 13 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - In Portugal, Circa 1933 November 13-21 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - In the Azores, 1933 November 21-23 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Over Madeira, 1933 November 26 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - In Bathurst, Gambia, 1933 December 1-5 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Circling SS Westfalen, 1933 December 6 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - In Brazil, 1933 December 6-12 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - In San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1933 December 15 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - In Miami, Florida, 1933 December 16 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Return to United States from North Atlantic survey flight.
  - Presentation of the Lockheed Sirius to the American Museum of Natural History, 1934 January 4 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Test flight of Pan American Airways Sikorsky S-42 Clipper, 1934 July 3 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Sikorsky Clipper S-42 flight crew, 1934 August 1 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - With monocoup plane in St. Louis, Missouri, 1934 September 2 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - In Oklahoma with Atkins family, 1934 September (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - In New Mexico, Circa 1934 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - At Bruno Hauptmann's trial, 1935 January 9 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - In Englewood, New Jersey, with relatives, 1935 April (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Passport photographs, Circa 1935 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - With Alexis Carrel and Ebeling, 1935 April 5 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - In North Haven, Maine, with relatives, 1935 August (Box 15, Folder 20-22)
  - In Roswell, New Mexico, 1936 February (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Working on Goddard's rocket launch.
  - At Long Barn in Kent, England, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - In Germany (album), Circa 1936-1937 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - In Berlin, Germany, 1936 July 22-August 1 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - In Copenhagen, Denmark, with Alexis Carrel, 1936 August 2 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - In St. Gildas, France, 1936 August (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Flying Miles Mohawk, 1936 October 27 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - In Ireland, 1936 November (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - In Rome, 1937 February (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - In Rhodes, Greece, 1937 February (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - In India, 1937 March (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - In Germany, 1937 October 12 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - In Illiec, France, 1938 June-July (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - In Russia, 1938 August 18-31 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - In Prague, Czech Republic, 1938 September 1-7 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - In P-36A fighter plane, 1939 April 21 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Seated, 1939 May 2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Negatives, Circa 1930s-1940s (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - At Air Force base, Circa 1939-1944 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - With unindentified people, Circa 1940s (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - With Jim Newton and Anne Morrow Lindbergh, 1940 January 21 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - National Advisory Committee of Aeronautics, 1940 April 18 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - With Igor Sikorsky, 1940 May 13 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - At Long Barn, Kent, England, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Trip to Florida with Jim Newton, 1941 March 6 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - At Ford plant, 1942 June (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Testing effects of altitude, 1942 September 22 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    At Mayo medical center in Rochester, Minnesota.
  - Passport photographs, Circa 1943 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - In Palm Springs and Beverly Hills, California, Circa 1943 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - With mule train, 1944 December 20 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Bell Aircraft Corporation, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - In South Pacific, 1944 May (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - With General McClure, 1944 May 21 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - On Emirau Island, South Pacific, 1944 May-June (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - With General Whitehead, 1944 July 1 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - With General Kenney, 1944 July 12 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - With Colonel McDonald in Hollandia, New Guinea, 1944 July 24 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - With R. Porter, P. Shanahan, and C. Huffsmith, Circa 1945 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - At Sikorsky plant, 1945 March 1 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - In Paris, France, 1945 May 13 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - On Naval technical mission in Garmisch, Germany, 1945 June 7 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Tribute to Thomas McGuire, 1946 May 8 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Philadelphia Navy tour, 1947 June 18-19 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - At Wright Aeronautics in Paterson, New Jersey, 1948 April 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - In Wichita, Kansas, 1948 July 1 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Inspection of the Air Force, 1948 November-1949 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - With Pan American Airways pilots, 1948 December 8 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Air Force base inspection in Fukora, Japan, Circa 1949 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Scott Air Force base, Illinois, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Receiving Wright brothers trophy at the Aero Club, Washington, 1949 December 17 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - In Bavaria, 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Fort Worth, Texas, with Major General R. M. Ramey, Circa 1950 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - In St. Gildas, France, 1950 April 9 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - At the Shields house, 1952 July 15 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - In Newburyport, Massachusetts, 1952 August (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Pan American Airways visit, 1953 August 26 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - In Georgetown, Washington, DC, 1953 September 14 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - At Glenn Martin Company in Baltimore, Maryland, Circa 1954 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Guggenheim medal, 1954 January 25 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Selecting Air Force Academy site, 1954 April 29 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Travelling with Pan American Airways, Circa 1955 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - On set of The Spirit of St. Louis film, Circa 1956 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Boeing Airline trip, 1956 February 23 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - At Rhein-Main air base, Germany, 1961 February 1 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - In Darien, Connecticut, Circa 1962 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - At Scotts Cove, Connecticut, Circa 1962 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - At Whitehouse Kennedy children, Circa 1962 (Box 18, Folder 24a)
  - In Kenya with Ian Grimwood, 1964 December (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - With Dr. Henderson, Laslo Schwartz, and Louise Schwartz, 1966 June (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - With officers, 1966 August (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - With Mr. Walker, Mr. and Mrs. Freundl, and Mr. Mills, Circa 1967 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Pan American Airways directors inspection trip, 1967 February (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - At Yale Medical School, 1967 March 28 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Udjung expedition, 1967 May (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - In Indonesia, 1967 June (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Observing heart surgery with Dr. Denton A. Cooley, 1967 October 10 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - In Baja, California, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Brazil conservation trip, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - In Taiwan, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Presentation of honorary degree at Georgetown University, Circa 1968 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - On Land Morrow Lindbergh's ranch in Montana, 1968 June (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Dinner for Apollo 8 astronauts at the White House, 1968 December (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - At Air Force academy with Majors McRaney and Means, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Airline Pilot Association meeting, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - In Cape May, New Jersey, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - In Hawaii, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Passport photographs, Circa 1969 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - With Apollo 8 astronauts, Frank Borman, James Lovell, and William Anders, Circa 1969 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Receiving conservation award from Will Rogers, 1969 July 11 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Grumman Aerospace Corporation dinner, 1969 July 15 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - In São Paulo, Brazil, 1969 August 28 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - With Juan Salcedo, Jr., 1969 September 2 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - New York Times interview, 1969 October 14 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - With Neil Armstrong, 1969 October 16 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - In Dallas, Texas, 1969 October 23 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - With Wernher von Braun and the lunar surface, 1969 November 28 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - In the Philippines, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - National Naval Medical Center, Circa 1970-1972 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Taken by Alfred R. Henderson, 1970 May 6 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - In Madagascar, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - In Kipahulu, Maui, with R. H. Coryell and S. Pryor, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - With Manda Ezilde, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - With Hilda Linley in Montauk Point, New York, Circa 1971 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - With B. Larson in Little Falls, Minnesota, 1971 March (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - At Regina Laudis In Bethlehem, Connecticut, 1971 August 6 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - In Australia, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - With Warren Meyer, Circa 1972 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - In Philippines, Circa 1972 January-May (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - In Mexico, 1972 March (Box 20, Folder 12)
    Includes a few newspaper clippings.
  - In Washington, DC, for recreation conference., 1972 August (Box 20, Folder 13)
    Includes photographs with Richard Nixon.
  - In Philippines, 1972 October (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - On board the Brigantine Rendezvous in San Diego, 1972 December (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - In Long Island, New York, for opening of Falais, 1973 May 16 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - At Georgetown University, 1973 June (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - At Paris airshow, 1973 June 3 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - With Eva (sister) in Little Falls, Minnesota, 1973 August 30 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - By airplane, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Anne Morrow Lindbergh, Circa 1906-1977; Series II
  The series is arranged as follows: portraits are filed first followed by all other photographs filed chronologically.
  The series consists of photographic prints and negatives of Anne Morrow Lindbergh, individually and with others, including family and friends. The photographs document Anne Morrow Lindbergh's childhood, family life, travels, leisure activities, writing career and honors.
  Photographs of Anne Morrow Lindbergh with Charles are filed in Series I, Charles Augustus Lindbergh, and with her children are filed in Series III, Charles Augustus Lindbergh and Anne Morrow Lindbergh family. Additional photographs of Anne are filed in Series V in the Morrow family groups and trips section. Oversized photographs are filed in Oversize at the end of the collection.
  - Portraits, Circa 1918-1929 (Box 21, Folder 1-4)
  - Infant years, Circa 1906-1910 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Ages six to ten, Circa 1911-1915 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Age eleven, Circa 1916 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Age twelve, Circa 1918 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Chapin School, Circa 1920 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Negatives, Circa 1920s-1930s (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - In the summer, 1923 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Age twenty-two?, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Portrait with Elizabeth Cutter Morrow, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Passport photographs, Circa 1929 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Age twenty-five, Circa 1929-1930 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Maternity Center luncheon, 1931 May 6 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - In Karugawa, Japan, 1931 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - In flying cap, 1931 August 3 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - In Maine, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - On a boat, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - On Atlantic survey flight, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - On steps, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - In North Haven, Maine, and other locations, 1934-1935 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Writing North to the Orient, 1935 January (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - General, 1936-1937 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - In Illiec, France, Circa 1936-1938 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - At desk in Long Barn, Kent, England, Circa 1938 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - In Berlin, Circa 1938 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Receiving honorary degree from Amherst College, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - General, Circa 1940 (Box 22A, Folder 1)
  - Passport photographs, Circa 1940 (Box 22A, Folder 2)
  - On sailboat in Florida, 1941 (Box 22A, Folder 3)
  - At Cranbrook, Circa 1943 (Box 22A, Folder 4)
  - With friends, Circa 1945 (Box 22A, Folder 5)
  - Trip to France, 1947 October 5-7 (Box 22A, Folder 6)
  - Trip to castle ruins, 1949 July (Box 22A, Folder 7)
  - Passport photographs, Circa 1950 (Box 22A, Folder 8)
  - In Newburyport, Massachusetts, 1950-1952 (Box 22A, Folder 9)
  - In Scotts Cove, Connecticut, Circa 1955 (Box 22A, Folder 10)
  - With seashell, Circa 1962 (Box 22A, Folder 11)
  - With friends, 1959-circa 1976 (Box 22A, Folder 12)
  - Receiving Edward Warner award, 1975 (Box 22A, Folder 13)
  - Receiving honorary degree from Middlebury College
    General
    See: Oversize
  - At Charles Augustus Lindbergh memorial fund, Circa 1976 (Box 22A, Folder 14)
    With Mrs. Augier and Ryoichi Sasakawa.
  - Opening of Lindbergh collection, 1977 (Box 22A, Folder 15)
  - In Maui, Hawaii, 1977 March (Box 22A, Folder 16)
  - Speech at Le Bourget airport, France, 1977 June 4 (Box 22A, Folder 17)
  - Unveiling Lindbergh statue in Minneapolis with Reeve, 1985 May (Box 22A, Folder 18)
- Charles Augustus Lindbergh and Anne Morrow Lindbergh family, 1930-circa 1979; Series III
  The series is arranged in two sections: Group and Individual. The Group photographs are arranged chronologically. The Individual photographs are filed by birth order and chronologically therein.
  The series consists of photographs of Anne and Charles with their children, Charles Augustus, Jr., Jon Morrow, Land Morrow, Anne Spencer, Scott Morrow, and Reeve Morrow, as well as photographs of the children together and individually. The series documents the Lindberghs as a family, primarily from 1930 to 1950. Many of the photographs in the series are portraits. Oversized photographs and albums are filed in Oversize at the end of the collection.
  - Group
    - 1930 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      Anne Morrow Lindbergh and Charles Augustus Lindbergh, Jr.
    - 1931 June (Box 23, Folder 2)
      Anne Morrow Lindbergh and Charles Augustus Lindbergh, Jr. in swimming pool.
    - 1931 June 22 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      Charles Augustus Lindbergh, Jr., first birthday.
    - 1931 July 29 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      Anne Morrow Lindbergh and Charles Augustus Lindbergh, Jr., at Englewood, New Jersey.
    - Circa 1932-1935 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Circa 1935 (Box 23, Folder 6)